# Matthew Lluís Web Developer

linkedin.com/in/mwlluis github.com/MattTheMicrowave mattthemicrowave.github.io/matthewlluis

## About Me ...

I am an Austin-based, full-stack Web Developer. I am experienced with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, along with the Bootstrap, Angular.js, Express.js, and Backbone.js frameworks, in addition to the Node.js platform. I like to build, I like to share, and I really (really) like to learn.

# Experience

February 2016 - present

khmertuktuk.com, khmertuktuk.com/spanish.html Webmaster/Web Developer

This is a website that I created and maintain for my friend's tuk-tuk service in Siem Reap, Cambodia. It was built from scratch in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I also built a Spanishlanguage version.

August 2015 – present

eyehategod.ee, facebook.com/OfficialEyehateGod Web Developer/Contributor/Administrator

These are the official websites of the New Orleans-based band, I maintain, design, and edit the client-side components of eyehategod.ee, coding in HTML, CSS, and Javascript languages.

May 2013 - present

#### thekingsofmetal.com/blog

Writer/Administrator

This is a travel blog site, built with WordPress, that I write for and maintain using the WordPress platform to edit and modify the layout and functionality of the content.

## Skills

Portfolio:

http://mattthemicrowave.github.io/matthewlluis/portfolio.html

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery,

PHP, Python

Frameworks: Bootstrap, Angular.js, Backbone.js, Express.js, Mongoose.js

Databases: MongoDB

Platforms: Node.js, Amazon Web Services

Software: Atom (text editor), Brackets (text editor), Git (command line), WordPress, Adobe Creative Suite. Microsoft Office Suite

Additional Languages: Fluency in Spanish (Conversing, Reading, Writing)

#### Education

**Austin Coding Academy,** Austin, TX Completed Full-Stack Advanced Track, 2016

**Speakeasy Language School,** Barcelona, Spain Completed Intensive Spanish Program, 2014

**The University of Texas at Austin**, Austin, TX PhD in Biochemistry, 2009

**University of South Florida**, Tampa, FL B.S. in Chemistry, 2004

#### Contact



(512) 806-9176



matthew.w.lluis@gmail.com